ipay88.com.my 2012-03-06

# iPay88: Privacy Policy

**Overview**

By accepting the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, you expressly consent to us in collecting, using and disclosing your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

**  
Data Protection & Security**

iPay88 protects your personal data against unauthorised access, use or disclosure.  All internet communication is secured using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security 128bit encryption. 

iPay88 is complied with PCI Data Security Standard & the following security features:

  * Antivirus software and hardware

  * Hardware firewall

  * DoS Attack Prevention

  * 3D-Secure Compliance ("Verified by Visa" (by Visa) and "MasterCard SecureCode" (by MasterCard))

However, you are advised to follow certain security practices yourself.  You must never share your Account or login details with anyone.  If you are concerned that any of your login details have been compromised, you can change them any time you like once you are logged on, and immediately contact our Customer Services.

**  
Collection and Use of Information**

iPay88 collects personal information to set up and manage accounts for our ecommerce services and to handle orders of goods and services from iPay88's Merchants.

You may need to provide iPay88 with personal information such as:

  * names; phone numbers; mailing, billing, shipping, and email addresses;

  * bank account information; credit and debit card information; dates of birth; and identification documents

iPay88 uses such information for:

  * website registration; enabling sales and other transactions; processing payments and settlement; sending payouts; handling orders; providing receipts;

  * providing customer service; providing dispute resolution, chargebacks, refunds, or related issues;

  * marketing and surveys; sending service update notices;

  * recovering debt and collections; detecting and preventing fraud; detecting and preventing violations of our legal agreements;

  * measuring, improving, and customizing our services; and

  * fulfilling other technical, logistical, financial, tax, legal, compliance, administrative, or back office functions.

iPay88 may also collect background information and credit checks from third parties to verify your identity; deter, detect, and prevent fraud and illegal activity; make business decisions; and as a part of our legal obligations.  iPay88 retains such information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

iPay88 will take appropriate steps to protect your privacy.  Whenever you provide sensitive information (for example, a credit card number to make a purchase), iPay88 will take reasonable steps to protect it.  iPay88 will also take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information in storage.

**  
Use of Cookies**

The Website uses "cookies" to identify a user's session on the Website and thereby offers continuity as the member moves around the site.  Cookies are only used on the Website to store non-critical data.  Cookies are pieces of information that websites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes.

Cookies allow websites to maintain user information across connections.  They are small strings of characters used by many websites to deliver data to your computer, and in certain circumstances, return the information to the website.  Cookies contain only information that members volunteer, and they do not have the capability of infiltrating a user's hard drive and stealing personal information.  The simple function of a cookie is that of helping the user navigate a website with as little obstruction as possible.

 ** **

**  
Third-Party Links**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our users, iPay88 may link to sites operated by third parties.  However, even if the third party is affiliated with iPay88, iPay88 has no control over these linked sites, all of which have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of iPay88.  These linked sites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk.

**  
Notification of Changes**

If iPay88 decides to change our privacy policy, iPay88 will post those changes on its website so the users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If, at any point, iPay88 decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, iPay88 will notify users by way of an e-mail.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.  iPay88 will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**  
Contact Information**

If you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement, you may contact us by email at [privacy@ipay88.com.my](mailto:privacy@ipay88.com) or by writing to us at:

Attn: Privacy Officer  
**iPay88**

No. 63 & 65, Jalan Jejaka 7  
Taman Maluri, Cheras   
55100 Kuala Lumpur   
Malaysia.

Tel No. : +603-92005555

Fax No. : +603-92003333
